<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TEAL on UNCOPIED, a blog for uncopiers</title>
    <link>https://blog.uncopied.art/tags/teal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in TEAL on UNCOPIED, a blog for uncopiers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.uncopied.art/tags/teal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>First entire virtual Art exhibition sold as a NFT</title>
      <link>https://blog.uncopied.art/blog/first-entire-virtual-art-exhibition-digitized-as-a-nft/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.uncopied.art/blog/first-entire-virtual-art-exhibition-digitized-as-a-nft/</guid>
      <description>On 2nd July, a collector acquired EPOCH, &amp;ldquo;FREEPORT&amp;rdquo;, 2021; 1/5 for $8,200 USD. This was the first of five limited edition NFT by EPOCH gallery, tokenizing the “FREEPORT” exhibition. In many respects, if was a first :
 the first entire virtual Art exhibition digitized as a NFT, the first NFT for a collective artwork managed with an Algorand smart contract, the first NFT secured by Uncopied and commercially sold, with its own physical document (certificate of authenticity and collector agreement).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Royalty smart contract in TEAL for Algorand NFTs</title>
      <link>https://blog.uncopied.art/blog/a-teal-smart-contract-to-manage-artistic-royalties-on-algorand/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.uncopied.art/blog/a-teal-smart-contract-to-manage-artistic-royalties-on-algorand/</guid>
      <description>A Quick Note on Uncopied In February 2021, we started to demo a new kind of Certificate of Authenticity (CoA) to several artists, galleries and museums. Our prototype combined a chirograph and an Algorand Standard Asset (ASA) to secure the origin of a physical or digital artwork.
The prototype worked great and we received some valuable feedback. We could feel the strong expectations from the Algorand community, as we were hoping to launch in May 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
