<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About on UNCOPIED, a blog for uncopiers</title>
    <link>https://uncopied.art/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About on UNCOPIED, a blog for uncopiers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://uncopied.art/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>UNCOPIED team</title>
      <link>https://uncopied.art/about/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://uncopied.art/about/team/</guid>
      <description>Core Team and Open Collective Elian CARSENAT Elian Carsenat is founder and visionary entrepreneur. He is passionate about the World’s cultures and languages and has founded NamSor in 2012, a piece of software to classify personal names by gender, country of origin or ethnicity. The big data tool can infer valuable data about 7 billion people, processing over one million names daily. With it, Elian and his team has helped countries reconnect with diaspora, attract FDIs, talents and jobs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UNCOPIED certificates are easy to make, hard to fake</title>
      <link>https://uncopied.art/about/chirograph/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://uncopied.art/about/chirograph/</guid>
      <description>Certificates of authenticity are physically secured using a chirograph Some physical and digital artwork produced today will make a difference in the World. Can anyone tell for sure whose creations will be distinguished in future times? Time will tell.
A certificate of authenticity is a promise made by a creator.
&amp;ldquo;It is ME, I did THIS, for YOU, and I claim : THIS is unique, it will change US.&amp;rdquo;
The ME, the YOU and the THIS should be explicite and last to make history.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
