<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>security on UNCOPIED, a blog for uncopiers</title>
    <link>https://blog.uncopied.art/tags/security/</link>
    <description>Recent content in security on UNCOPIED, a blog for uncopiers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.uncopied.art/tags/security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Can the blockchain help secure museum collections?</title>
      <link>https://blog.uncopied.art/blog/blockchain-museum-collection-inventory/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.uncopied.art/blog/blockchain-museum-collection-inventory/</guid>
      <description>Preparing for the aftermath of COVID-19: our cultural heritage is at risk A 2011 survey by ICCROM/UNESCO has revealed that up to 60% of museum collections are endangered globally. Storage overloads, poor conditions for conservation and budget constraints contribute to risk factors. 95% of a museum’s collections are kept in storage. Billions of objects are kept away from public sight. One in four museums have incomplete documentation systems. One in 10 museums, or less, have made their entire collections digitally accessible with pictures and metadata.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UNCOPIED I: The Grand Hall</title>
      <link>https://blog.uncopied.art/blog/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.uncopied.art/blog/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>Will UNCOPIED certificates, or the idea of it, survive the blaze of time?
Citing Hugo,
 Three hundred and forty-eight years, six months, and nineteen days ago to-day, the Parisians awoke to the sound of all the bells in the triple circuit of the city, the university, and the town ringing a full peal.
  The sixth of January, 1482, is not, however, a day of which history has preserved the memory.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
