<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Making original truly unique. on UNCOPIED, a blog for uncopiers</title>
    <link>https://uncopied.art/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Making original truly unique. on UNCOPIED, a blog for uncopiers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://uncopied.art/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Royalty smart contract in TEAL for Algorand NFTs</title>
      <link>https://uncopied.art/blog/a-teal-smart-contract-to-manage-artistic-royalties-on-algorand/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://uncopied.art/blog/a-teal-smart-contract-to-manage-artistic-royalties-on-algorand/</guid>
      <description>A Quick Note on Uncopied In February 2021, we started to demo a new kind of Certificate of Authenticity (CoA) to several artists, galleries and museums. Our prototype combined a chirograph and an Algorand Standard Asset (ASA) to secure the origin of a physical or digital artwork.
The prototype worked great and we received some valuable feedback. We could feel the strong expectations from the Algorand community, as we were hoping to launch in May 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UNCOPIED team</title>
      <link>https://uncopied.art/about/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://uncopied.art/about/team/</guid>
      <description>Core Team and Open Collective Elian CARSENAT Elian Carsenat is founder and visionary entrepreneur. He is passionate about the World’s cultures and languages and has founded NamSor in 2012, a piece of software to classify personal names by gender, country of origin or ethnicity. The big data tool can infer valuable data about 7 billion people, processing over one million names daily. With it, Elian and his team has helped countries reconnect with diaspora, attract FDIs, talents and jobs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UNCOPIED certificates are easy to make, hard to fake</title>
      <link>https://uncopied.art/about/chirograph/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://uncopied.art/about/chirograph/</guid>
      <description>Certificates of authenticity are physically secured using a chirograph Some physical and digital artwork produced today will make a difference in the World. Can anyone tell for sure whose creations will be distinguished in future times? Time will tell.
A certificate of authenticity is a promise made by a creator.
&amp;ldquo;It is ME, I did THIS, for YOU, and I claim : THIS is unique, it will change US.&amp;rdquo;
The ME, the YOU and the THIS should be explicite and last to make history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can the blockchain help secure museum collections?</title>
      <link>https://uncopied.art/blog/blockchain-museum-collection-inventory/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://uncopied.art/blog/blockchain-museum-collection-inventory/</guid>
      <description>Preparing for the aftermath of COVID-19: our cultural heritage is at risk A 2011 survey by ICCROM/UNESCO has revealed that up to 60% of museum collections are endangered globally. Storage overloads, poor conditions for conservation and budget constraints contribute to risk factors. 95% of a museum’s collections are kept in storage. Billions of objects are kept away from public sight. One in four museums have incomplete documentation systems. One in 10 museums, or less, have made their entire collections digitally accessible with pictures and metadata.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UNCOPIED I: The Grand Hall</title>
      <link>https://uncopied.art/blog/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://uncopied.art/blog/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>Will UNCOPIED certificates, or the idea of it, survive the blaze of time?
Citing Hugo,
 Three hundred and forty-eight years, six months, and nineteen days ago to-day, the Parisians awoke to the sound of all the bells in the triple circuit of the city, the university, and the town ringing a full peal.
  The sixth of January, 1482, is not, however, a day of which history has preserved the memory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://uncopied.art/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://uncopied.art/contact/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;d love to hear from you, let&amp;rsquo;s schedule a quick Zoom via Calendly,
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
